Today, we're using data science
to reach people trapped in the most devastating of circumstances.
Medical treatments are advancing at a rigorous pace,
thanks to a deeper data-driven understanding of the human body.
Armed with data, companies are improving
user experiences and building better products to power the future.
Hi, I'm Josh.
And I'm Louis. Data science is bringing together
statistics and computer science to solve real-world problems in every industry.
You are about to start on an awesome journey.
And we're very excited to welcome you to the data science nano degree program.
We've created this program to give you the tools
and experience to tackle any challenge with data.
We've partnered with industry leaders to help you
learn the best practices and build amazing projects.
Our goal, is to help you master the tools
you need to be an industry ready data scientist.
Let's do this.