In the next few years, software developers will need to know how to
incorporate deep learning models into everyday applications.
Anything with a camera will be using an image classification,
object detection, and face recognition,
and so on, all based on deep learning models.
For is user interfaces like Alexa, Cortana,
and Google Assistant all powered by
speech recognition models will become more and more common.
So, in this project,
you'll be implementing an image classification application.
This app will train a deep learning model on a data set of images,
then use the trained model to classify images.
First, you'll develop your code in
a Jupyter notebook to make sure your training implementation works.
Then, you'll convert the code to
a Python application that runs from the command line. Good luck.