Hi, I'm Gina.
I'm Josh.
We're here to share some tips on how to help you succeed in this Nanodegree program.
So, Josh, you've seen a lot of students go do this program. What's your advice?
Yeah. So, I think one of the the biggest things is,
to be successful in the program,
you have to be a really active learner.
What that means is, not just watching all the videos,
but also a lot of our most successful students take notes,
and they take really good notes,
so whether that's like screenshots of the videos and then written notes underneath,
type out notes or for me,
I actually like just writing things in a notepad that I carry around with me,
and then I can look at later.
Also, just when there's coding,
writing the code yourself.
So I think one of the biggest things is you have to write
code to learn how to code and sometimes that's just a lot of repetition.
Beyond that, there's a lot of things to do with
time management and how do you manage your time to be a successful student.
Sure. Managing time is definitely
a very tricky component that has a big contribution to success.
But what we've seen is that students who are most
successful come to the classroom at least two times a week.
So, just making sure you make that habit
of going to the classroom regularly can make a huge difference.
There's lots of ways to do that.
Yeah. Whether that's through like mobile apps or just like blocking out time on
your calendar and just keeping that on your daily routine.
But everything is dependent on your background,
what your learning style is,
and which parts of the course might be newer to you or easier for you.
So, in the end is getting to know what
your pace is and setting expectations for yourself,
and being open to adjusting your time estimations
can really help you succeed in the program.
So, sometimes maybe a particular quiz in a lesson might
take you a lot longer than other parts of the lesson and
sometimes this can be really good because it can help reinforce
your understanding and really develop your knowledge in that specific topic,
but sometimes it could take way longer than you want to you,
and it can be frustrating.
Do you have any advice on how to deal with these situations?
Yeah. So, I'll call those blockers,
and I think we all get them.
I think there's two big ways to sort of like address blockers.
One is to use the community.
So, there are a lot of students who just went
through the content that you might be struggling with,
and they can oftentimes point you in the right direction.
So, for that, we have Slack,
and I would strongly recommend being a part of the Slack community.
There are tons of resources that are posted in there,
and a lot of us are even active in there to help students.
Then the second thing is just being able to Google well.
Googling is a skill in of itself.
I think that whether it's being able to take
like an error from your code and search it or read through
the documentation or whether you're trying to really grasp
a large project and you're looking through an entire blog posts or co-post,
all of those things can help you better internalize the content
and even solve just small snips that might be happening in your code.
So we hope these tips can help you,
but in the end, learning is really a mindset,
and everyone is going to struggle.
You have to go into this knowing that it's going to be
challenging and just making sure your patient with
yourself and determined to make sure
this is the best learning experience for you can really help you succeed.
Yeah. So, thank you.
We hope that our tips can help you be successful with your Nanodegree program.