At Udacity, we believe in a few things.
We believe that learning is a lifelong journey.
So we build programs that help you learn cutting-edge skills for jobs of the future.
We believe that you learn best by getting your hands dirty with the real work.
You become stronger by learning from your experiences and your mistakes.
Whether that's through quizzes, projects,
discussions with other students or Udacity staff,
or researching problems online.
Through this Nanodegree program,
you will learn the skills you need to develop
an intuition for solving problems in the field.
We aim to give you the best learning experience by providing the framework,
tools and support you need to be successful.
If something isn't clear at any point,
please reach out in Slack,
email, or through the classroom feedback channels.
With that said, welcome to the Data Science Nanodegree Program.
You're about to embark on an incredible journey,
and we're so excited to be joining you.